Hello everyone,
Okutman: Herkese
and welcome to the lecture, How to Approach This Course.
merhaba ve bu Kursa Yaklam Dersine ho geldiniz.
This lecture will go over the basics
Bu derste bu dersin en iyi
of how to get the most out of this course.
ekilde nasl alnlacann temelleri zerinde durulacaktr.
Now, people who are taking this course
imdi, bu dersi alanlar
hopefully fall within three categories.
umarm  kategoriye girer.
Beginners who have never programmed before,
balayanlar, baka bir dilden gelen
programmers coming in from another language,
programclar veya ara Python programclar.
or intermediate Python programmers.
Daha nce hi programlamayan yeni
Now I'm going to discuss how you should approach this
imdi hangi kategoride olduunuza gre bu
course depending on what category you're in.
kursa nasl yaklamanz gerektiini tartacam.
First, beginners who have never programmed.
lk nce, hi programlamayan yeni balayanlar.
Complete beginners should read the notebooks
Yeni balayanlar, ekran grntlerini izlemeden nce
before watching the screen casts.
dizst bilgisayarlarn okumaldr.
Then, watch the screen cast and follow along.
Ardndan, ekran grntsn izle ve takip edin.
Then, you should take the quiz, or test,
veya karlk gelen dev devlerini almalsnz.
or corresponding homework assignments
Ardndan, anlaynz kontrol etmek
to check for your understanding.
iin testi veya testi
Afterwards, make sure to review the written notebook
Daha sonra, dersin materyalini tam olarak anlayabildiinizden
to make sure you full understood
emin olmak iin yazl
the lecture's material.
defteri gzden geirdiinizden emin olun.
Now, if you're a programmer coming in from another language,
imdi, baka bir dilde gelen bir
you should read the lecture notebooks and follow along.
programc iseniz, ders not defterlerini okumal ve birlikte takip etmelisiniz.
Then, if something isn't clear,
edin ve ekran grntsn izleyin.
go ahead and watch the screen cast.
Ardndan, bir ey net deilse, devam
Afterwards, you should take the quiz, test,
Ardndan, snav, testi veya karlk
or corresponding homework assignment
gelen ev devini yapmal
and make sure you can check your understanding
ve anladnz ekran st
either through the screen cast
yaz araclyla veya not defteri
or through the notebook.
araclyla kontrol edebildiinden emin olmalsn.
Finally, for intermediate Python programmers,
programclar iin defteri okumal ve konuyu
you should read the notebook
bildiinizden emin olmalsn.
and make sure you know the topic.
Son olarak, ara Python
If you're and intermediate Python programmer,
Python programcs iseniz ve
you can probably skip the first few sections
aradnz kiiyseniz, muhtemelen Python'un temellerini
of the course where we discuss Python basics.
tarttmz kursun ilk birka blmn atlayabilirsiniz.
Once you're at the advanced topics,
Bir kez gelimi konularda olduunuzda,
I would recommend you read the notebooks
defterleri okumanz ve bu dersden
and watch the screen casts
en iyi sonucu alabilmeniz
to get the most out of this course.
iin ekran grntlerini izlemenizi neririm.
And do the corresponding either test,
Ve dersin bu blmnde ilgili
quiz, or homework assignment for that section
test, ksa snav veya ev
of the course.
devi yapn.
Now, discussing questions.
imdi, tartmak sorular.
If after watching the screen cast or checking the notebook
Ekran grntsn izledikten sonra veya dizst bilgisayar
something doesn't make sense,
kontrol ederek bir eyler mantkl
feel free to start a discussion in the forums.
gelmezse forumlarda bir tartma balatmaya ekinmeyin.
Remember to check if there is a FAQ,
olmadn kontrol etmeyi unutmayn.
Frequently Asked Questions lecture
Konuyla ilgili bir SSS, Ska
corresponding with the lecture.
Sorulan Sorular dersinin olup
As this course gets populated with more students,
Bu ders daha fazla renci
more FAQ lectures will begin to pop up
ile doldurulduunda, ders boyunca
throughout the course.
daha fazla SSS dersi balayacaktr.
Also, remember to use the search feature
Ayrca, daha hzl sonular iin
in the discussion section for faster results.
tartma blmndeki arama zelliini kullanmay unutmayn.
Alright, that's it for this section of the course.
Pekl, dersin bu blm iin bu kadar.
Up next, we'll learn how to instal Python
Daha sonra, Python'u bilgisayarlarmza nasl kuracanz
on our computers, and go over the basic course environment.
ve temel kurs ortamn nasl reneceimizi reneceiz.
Thank you, and I will see you at the next lecture.
Teekkrler, bir sonraki derside grrz.